<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Simone Barbieri</title>
    <link>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Simone Barbieri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://barbierisimone.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BlueBlueRunning</title>
      <link>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/bluebluerunning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/bluebluerunning/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Barbieri Simone, Loddo Andrea, Mameli Emanuele, Muntoni Alessandro, Pompianu Livio
University project: Final Project for the unit Operating System 2 for the Master Degree in Computer Science at the University of Cagliari.
A five people project which consists in an Android application which traks user&amp;rsquo;s running trainings and it allows the users to save locally (in .GPX format) and share them with Google services such as Google Spreadsheet, Google Drive, Google Maps and Google Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voronoi Clarke &amp; Wright Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/voronoi-clarke-wright-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/voronoi-clarke-wright-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>Authors: Barbieri Simone, Loddo Andrea, Mameli Emanuele, Muntoni Alessandro, Pompianu Livio
University project: Final Project for the unit Operative Research for the Master Degree in Computer Science at the University of Cagliari.
A five people project which implements a modified version of Clarke and Wright Algorithm, for the vehicle routing problem, using the Voronoi tasselation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convex Hull 3D</title>
      <link>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/convex-hull-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/convex-hull-3d/</guid>
      <description>University project: Final Project for the unit Algorithms and Data Structures 2 for the Master Degree in Computer Science at the University of Cagliari.
It implements a Convex Hull of a set of points in a 3D space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooter Pacman</title>
      <link>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/shooter-pacman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbierisimone.com/projects/shooter-pacman/</guid>
      <description>University project: Final Project for the unit Operating System for the Bachelor Degree in Computer Science at the University of Cagliari.
A version of the famous videogame Pacman, in which Pacman and the ghost can shoot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>