<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Publications on Simone Barbieri</title><link>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/</link><description>Recent content in Publications on Simone Barbieri</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://barbierisimone.com/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3D Content Creation Exploiting 2D Character Animation</title><link>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/3d-content-creation-exploiting-2d-character-animation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/3d-content-creation-exploiting-2d-character-animation/</guid><description>Authors Barbieri Simone, Centre for Digital Entertainment, Bournemouth University, Thud Media
Jiang Tao, Bournemouth University
Cawthorne Ben, Thud Media
Xiao Zhidong, Bournemouth University
Yang Xiaosong, Bournemouth University
Abstract This poster proposes a new system for the generation of 3D content by using existing 2D character animations. The system is fully automatic. The assets required are directly available from the 2D animation production pipeline, and therefore the system could be easily integrated in it.</description></item><item><title>Repurpose 2D Character Animations for a VR Environment using BDH Shape Interpolation</title><link>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/repurpose-2d-character-animations-for-a-vr-environment-using-bdh-shape-interpolation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/repurpose-2d-character-animations-for-a-vr-environment-using-bdh-shape-interpolation/</guid><description>Authors Barbieri Simone, Centre for Digital Entertainment, Bournemouth University, Thud Media
Ben Cawthorne, Thud Media
Xiao Zhidong, Bournemouth University
Yang Xiaosong, Bournemouth University
Abstract Virtual Reality technology has spread rapidly in recent years. However, its growth risks ending soon due to the absence of quality content, except for few exceptions. We present an original framework that allows artists to use 2D characters and animations in a 3D Virtual Reality environment, in order to give an easier access to the production of content for the platform.</description></item><item><title>An interactive editor for curve-skeletons: SkeletonLab</title><link>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/an-interactive-editor-for-curve-skeletons-skeletonlab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/an-interactive-editor-for-curve-skeletons-skeletonlab/</guid><description>Authors Barbieri Simone, Centre for Digital Entertainment, Bournemouth University
Meloni Pietro, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Usai Francesco, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Spano Davide Lucio, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Scateni Riccardo, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Abstract Curve-skeletons are powerful shape descriptors able to provide higher level information on topology, structure and semantics of a given digital object. Their range of application is wide and encompasses computer animation, shape matching, modelling and remeshing.</description></item><item><title>Enhancing character posing by a sketch-based interaction</title><link>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/enhancing-character-posing-by-a-sketch-based-interaction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/enhancing-character-posing-by-a-sketch-based-interaction/</guid><description>Authors Barbieri Simone, Centre for Digital Entertainment, Bournemouth University
Garau Nicola, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Hu Wenyu, Gannan Normal University
Xiao Zhidong, Bournemouth University
Yang Xiaosong, Bournemouth University
Abstract Sketch as the most intuitive and powerful 2D design method has been used by artists for decades. However it is not fully integrated into current 3D animation pipeline as the difficulties of interpreting 2D line drawing into 3D. Several successful research for character posing from sketch has been presented in the past few years, such as the Line of Action [Guay et al.</description></item><item><title>Skeleton Lab: an Interactive Tool to Create, Edit, and Repair Curve-Skeletons</title><link>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/skeletonlab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://barbierisimone.com/publications/skeletonlab/</guid><description>Authors Barbieri Simone, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Meloni Pietro, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Usai Francesco, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Scateni Riccardo, Universitá degli studi di Cagliari
Abstract Curve-skeletons are well known shape descriptors, able to encode topological and structural information of a shape. The range of applications in which they are used comprises, to name a few, computer animation, shape matching, modelling and remeshing. Different tools for automatically extracting the curve-skeleton for a given input mesh are currently available, as well as inverse skeletonization tools, where a user-defined skeleton is taken as input in order to build a mesh that reflects the encoded structure.</description></item></channel></rss>